http://www.bostonnote.com/privacy-policy

Want an immediate cash offer?
Privacy Policy
The Boston Note Company (BNC) respects the privacy of its customers, clients, and visitors. If you have any questions about the operation of our website, please write to mail@bostonnote.com.Our website collects names, email addresses, and other personal information from customers, clients, and visitors only when submitted via one of our online forms, such as our Note Quote Form. This data is used solely by BNC and is not shared, traded, or sold to third parties unless customers or registrants opt to proceed with the sale of their loans, in which case we share only names, email addresses, and postal addresses with those that are required to know in order to complete the loan sale transaction.Registrants can un-register by writing to the email address above. Once you have established a customer account with us, you can opt-out of future promotional mailings by writing to the email address above.Our web-server also records IP addresses from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, to analyze trends, to track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information-all for the purpose of continually improving our website and delivering personalized, custom content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and their collection is standard procedure in most web-server environments.By filling out our forms at www.bostonnote.com, you signify your agreement to our privacy policy as stated above. Note that this policy may be revised periodically without notice. Please re-read this policy prior to submitting any personal information if you have concerns about how your information is being collected and used.
Quick & Reliable We are available via fax, email or telephone
Call 800-932-8933
Location PO Box 727Tyngsborough, MA 01879
Email mail@bostonnote.com
Call 800-932-8933
Leading the Nation In Privately Held Loan Acquisitions Since 1991
Share by:
